A Guide to the Barksdale Theatre Records 1945-2006 (bulk 1954-2004)
Library of Virginia
- Series IX. Miscellaneous, 1945-1998., Extent: 1.05 cu. ft. (3 boxes). (Box 56-58)
  - Richmond Comprehensive Theatre Program n.d. (Box-folder 58:11)
  - Richmond Public Relations Association 1990-1993 (Box-folder 58:12)
  - School of the Performing Arts in the Richmond Community (SPARC) 1994-1997 (Box-folder 58:13)
  - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), Calendar of events 1997 (Box-folder 58:14)
  - University of Alabama, Brochure 1997 (Box-folder 58:15)
- Series X. Scrapbooks, 1950-2000., Extent: 4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 59-62)
  The Scrapbook Series is housed in 7 boxes and arranged chronologically by date. The scrapbooks include advertisements, articles, photographs, programs, reviews, and telegrams of the Barksdale Theatre shows, 1954-2000. Of note is the scrapbook which includes reviews and programs from Longwood College and Virginia Museum Theatre.
  - Scrapbook, Longwood College, Virginia Museum Theatre, and Barksdale 1950-1957 (Box 59)
    Reviews, programs, telegrams
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1953-1957 (Box 59)
    Reviews and articles
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1955-1997 (Box 59)
    Reviews and articles. Many used in Going On...The First Thirty One Years book
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1973-1975 (Box 59)
  - Loose leaves, miscellaneous scrapbook pages ca. 1970-1980 (Box 59)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1955-1958 (Box 60)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1957-1964 (Box 60)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1973-1979 (Box 60)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1953-1975 (Box 61)
    Reviews, photographs, advertisements, articles
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1964-1969 (Box 61)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1966 (Box 61)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1968-1979 (Box 62)
    Reviews, photographs, articles, and signed copies of programs
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1969-1971 (Box 62)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1971-1980 (Box 62)
  - Scrapbook 1981 (Box 62)
    Articles and photographs regarding bicentennial celebration in Yorktown and Hanover Tavern County Fair
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1997-2000 (Box 62)
    Reviews, advertisements, and articles
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1971-1973 (Volume On shelf)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1973-1976 (Volume On shelf)
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1975-1982 (Volume On Shelf)
    Reviews, articles, and transcripts of TV reviews from WTVR and WRVA
  - Scrapbook, Barksdale 1976-1980 (Volume On shelf)
    Reviews, photographs, and articles
- Series XI. Oversize, 1954-2003., Extent: 2.1 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box 63-68)
  The Oversize Series is housed in 6 oversize boxes and 1 oversized drawer and arranged alphabetically into four subseries. Subseries have been designated for Artwork, Clippings and Reviews, Posters, and Miscellaneous.
  - Subseries 1: Artwork ca. 1954-1979
    Subseries 1: Artwork (ca. 1954-1979)
    This subseries is housed in 1 oversize box and includes sketches from Picnic (1960) by Helen Hull, sketches of women's costumes, a cartoon drawing of Muriel McAuley, and an oil painting of possibly a scene from Antigone, 1954.
    - Sketches from "Picnic" by Helen Hull 1960 (Oversize 63)
      5 sketches
    - Sketch of an unknown woman 1968 (Oversize 63)
    - Sketch of women's costumers from ca. 1890-1900 (Oversize 63)
    - Cartoon drawing of Muriel McAuley, "As busy as a one armed paper hanger" 1979 (Oversize 63)
    - Oil painting, possibly of "Antigone," by G.N. Buck 1954 (Oversize 63)
  - Subseries 2: Clippings and reviews 1990-2001
    Subseries 2: Clippings and reviews (1990-2001)
    This subseries is housed in 1 oversize box and 1 oversized drawer and arranged chronologically by date. Included are reviews from the Richmond Times Dispatch and Style Weekly on Barksdale shows including Golf with Alan Shepard, Three Tall Women, Red, Hot, and Cole, The Rocky Horror Picture Show, The Young Man from Atlanta, Inherit the Wind, She Loves Me, Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, Ella and Her Fella, Frank, and the Taming of the Shrew. Also included are articles on Pete Kilgore, Randy Strawderman, and the history of Hanover Tavern.
    - Oscar Wilde 1882/7/12 (Oversize 64)
      Richmond Daily Dispatch (reprint)
    - Hanover Tavern sold, by Robert Merritt 1990/1/10 (Oversize 64)
      RTD
    - Three Tall Women review, Tim Appelo 1994/3/14 (Oversize 64)
      The Nation
    - Three Tall Women writer Edward Albee, David Richards 1994/4/13 (Oversize 64)
      NY Times
    - Red, Hot, and Cole review, Roy Proctor 1997/11/24 (Oversize 64)
    - Red, Hot, and Cole review, S. Edward Stuart 1997/12/16 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
      SW
    - Red, Hot, and Cole review, S. Edward Stuart 1997/12/16 (Oversize 64)
    - The Young Man From Atlanta review, Roy Proctor 1998/4/20 (Oversize 64)
    - Rocky Horror Picture Show review, Roy Proctor 1998/5/21 (Oversize 64)
    - Rocky Horror Picture Show review, D.L. Hintz 1998/6/30 (Oversize 64)
    - Rocky Horror Picture Show review, Roy Proctor 1998/7/10 (Oversize 64)
    - Inherit the Wind review, D.L. Hintz 1998/10/6 (Oversize 64)
    - Inherit the Wind review 1998/10/23 (Oversize 64)
    - She Loves Me review, Roy Proctor 1998/11/23 (Oversize 64)
    - She Loves Me review, Richard Bell 1998/12/3 (Oversize 64)
      The Freelance Star
    - She Loves Me review 1998/12/3 (Oversize 64)
    - Article about Randy Strawderman 1999/2/9 (Oversize 64)
    - Article on Shaun DuPriest, by Dorothy Rowley 1999/5/5 (Oversize 64)
      The Petersburg Monitor
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat review, D.L. Hintz 1999/5/25 (Oversize 64)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat review, Roy Proctor 1999 (Oversize 64)
    - The Old Settler review, D.L. Hintz 1999 (Oversize 64)
    - Golf with Alan Shepard review, Roy Proctor 1999 (Oversize 64)
    - Violet 1999/10/5 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
    - Ella and her Fella, Frank review, D.L. Hintz 1999/11/2 (Oversize 64)
    - Ella and her Fella, Frank review, D.L. Hintz 1999/11/2 (Oversize 64)
    - Ella and her Fella, Frank review, Roy Proctor 1999/11/7 (Oversize 64)
    - Hurricane review, Julinda Lewis-Ferguson 2001/3/1 (Oversize 64)
      Richmond Free Press
    - Taming of the Shrew review, Jennifer C. Dodge 2001/4/12 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
    - David 'Pete' Kilgore, by Roy Proctor Unknown (Oversize 64)
      Richmond Times Dispatch
    - Golf with Alan Shepard review, Roy Proctor Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - Rocky Horror Picture Show review Unknown (Oversize 64)
      Culpepper Star Exponent
    - Reprint of Hanover Tavern history Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - To be young, gifted, and black review, Carole Kass Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - Reprint photographs from The River Niger Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - Three Tall Women review, Roy Proctor Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - Joseph and the Amazing review, Roy Proctor Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - The Woman in Black review, Roy Proctor Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - Three Tall Women review, D.L. Hintz Unknown (Oversize 64)
      Style Weekly
    - Inherit the Wind review, Roy Proctor Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - Old Settler review, D.L. Hintz Unknown (Oversize 64)
    - Sisters Rosensweig review, D.L. Hintz Unknown (Oversize 64)
  - Subseries 3: Posters 1980-2003
    This subseries is housed in 3 boxes and contains posters and mounted broadsides. Also included are seasonal posters and miscellaneous posters celebrating anniversaries of the Barksdale Theatre, and film and draft copies of posters.
    - Season poster 1980 (Oversize 65)
    - The Elephant Man (by Bill Nelson) 1982 (Oversize 65)
    - Gertrude Stein 1982 (Oversize 65)
    - Sweeney Todd 1982 (Oversize 65)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat 1984 (Oversize 65)
    - The Circle 1986 (Oversize 65)
    - Morning's at Seven 1986 (Oversize 65)
    - Brighton Beach Memoirs 1986 (Oversize 65)
    - Taking my turn 1986 (Oversize 65)
    - The Amorous Flea 1987 (Oversize 65)
    - A Child's Christmas in Wales 1988 (Frame 65)
    - Hot Grog 1988 (Frame 65)
    - Season poster 1989 (Oversize 65)
    - Season poster 1990 (Oversize 65)
    - Season poster 1991 (Oversize 65)
    - Season poster 1992 (Oversize 65)
    - Season poster 1993 (Oversize 65)
    - Bojangles 1993 (Oversize 65 (also in oversize drawer))
    - Falsettos 1994 (Oversize 65)
    - The World Goes Round 1994 (Oversize 65)
    - Season poster 1995 (Oversize 65)
    - Once on this Island 1995 (Oversize 65)
    - Born Yesterday 1995 (Oversize 65)
    - The Glass Menagerie 1995 (Oversize 65)
    - Weird Romance 1995 (Oversize 65)
    - Prelude to a Kiss 1995 (Oversize 65)
    - Blues in the Night 1997 (Oversize 65)
    - Love! Valour! Compassion 1997 (Oversize 65)
    - The Complete Works of Wllm Shkspr 1997 (Oversize 65)
    - Molly Sweeney 1997 (Oversize 65)
    - Red, Hot, and Cole 1997 (Oversize 65)
    - The Woman in Black 1997 (Oversize 65)
    - Season poster 1997 (Oversize 65)
    - Rocky Horror Picture Show 1998 (Oversize 65)
    - From the Mississippi Delta 1998 (Oversize 65)
    - The Young Man from Atlanta 1998 (Oversize 65)
    - Season poster 1998 (Oversize 65)
    - Ella and Her Fella, Frank 1999 (Oversize 65)
    - The Old Settler 1999 (Oversize 65)
    - Side Man 2000 (Oversize 65)
    - Carousel 2000 (Oversize 65)
    - Season membership brochure poster board 2000 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
    - Season brochure poster board 2000-2001 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
    - Proof 2003 (Oversize 65)
    - Nunsense Unknown (Oversize 65)
    - The Misadventures of Dr. Wolfgang Mortichi (Children's story telling) Unknown (Oversize 65)
    - Miscellaneous posters 1953-1999 (Oversize 66)
      25 years of Barksdale (1953-1978) by Pete Butzuer; 30 years of Barksdale (1953-1993); 1953-1981 Barksdale sign in sheet; 1954/1955 Gold in the Hills mark up poster; 1940's Radio Hour example/mark up posters; Sweeney Todd poster film, 1982; From the Mississippi Delta poster film, 1998; Inherit the Wind blow up of Scopes Monkey trial news items viewed in lobby display, 1998 October; Inherit the Wind example/mark up posters, 1998; Ella and Her Fella, Frank poster film, 1999; Before and after photograph scans of new Barksdale theatre in Willow Lawn; Randolph Macon faculty award to Pete Kilgore, n.d.; Theatre IV posters for Peter Pan and a season program, n.d.; Scott Joplin's, Treemunisha, at Dogwood Dell, n.d.; Bill Nelson posters; Jazz at the Barksdale poster (rolled); 1997 season program brochure mark ups
    - Ella and Her Fella posterboard with original drawings from 1999 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), The Glass Menagerie 1995 (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), Prelude to a Kiss 1995 (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), Weird Romance 1995 (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), Born Yesterday 1995 (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), The Search for Signs of Intelligent Life 1995 (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), The Trip to Bountiful 1996 (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), Das Barbecue 1996 (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), The Taffetas 1996 (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), Man of La Mancha Unknown (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), Agnes of God Unknown (Oversize 67)
    - Mounted broadside (black and white), Nunsense Unknown (Oversize 67)
  - Subseries 4: Miscellaneous 1971-2000
    This subseries is housed in 1 oversize box and 1 oversize drawer. Included are architectural drawings, awards, and correspondence. Included is a lighting plot for the bus tour of Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, 1986; sketch of a stage setting for Inherit the Wind; sketch of a general floor plan for Red, Hot, and Cole; architectural drawings of Hanover Tavern by the Historic American Building Survey, 1992; and correspondence and sketches from Hanson Associates, 1990, including basement and first floor plans of Hanover Tavern. Also included are award certificates from the Art Directors Club and numerous Phoebe Awards, 1976-1988, for Barksdale actors.
    - Miscellaneous items 1976-1992 (Oversize 68)
      Computer list of mailer addresses; I Miss that Mississippi Miss that Misses Me, Sheet music; Phoebe Awards received by Barksdale Theatre actors, 1976-1988; The Art Directors Club 62nd Annual Exhibition 1983 Merit Award to the Barksdale for Sweeney Todd; Quotes for the 2nd Annual Young Writers For the Theatre New Play Festival, Studio Theatre of Richmond; Hanover Tavern Project drawings and specifications, 1992, by Historic American Building Survey (13 sheets); Sketch of general floor plan setting for Red, Hot, and Cole, designed by Tim Priddy, 1976
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat Lighting plot, 1986-1987 bus and truck tour 1986, Drawing 1 of 2 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
    - Letter, from William H. Hartsock, President, Barksdale, to the Friends of Barksdale, regarding upcoming season, fundraising, and membership February 2000 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
    - Sketch of stage setting for probably Inherit the Wind 1998 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
    - Correspondence and sketches from Hanson Associates 1990 (Oversize Cabinet 22, Drawer 6)
      Includes sketch of Hanover Tavern parking area; basement floor plan of Hanover Tavern; and 1st floor plan of Hanover Tavern
    - Poster, "Jazz at the Barksdale" n.d. (Oversize On shelf, rolled)
- Series XII. Photographs, 1954-1999., Extent: 10.15 cu. ft. (29 boxes). (Box 69-97)
  The Photographs Series is housed in 29 boxes and arranged into seven subseries. Subseries have been designated for People, Plays, Buildings, Contact sheets, Negatives, Slides, and Miscellaneous. Included are hundreds of photographs documenting the numerous shows and actors involved with Barksdale over the course of the last 50 years, 1954-2004. Many of the photographs were identified but as the collection was being processed, Pete Kilgore and other former Barksdale actors were able to identify other photographs that were not known. Within each subseries the photographs are arranged by size, 8 1/2" x 11", 11" x 17", and 20"x 24".
  - Subseries 1: People.
    This subseries is housed in 3 boxes, with the unidentified photographs arranged to the rear. Included are photographs of many of the early Barksdale actors, including Betsy Chadwell, Fred Haseltine, Helen Hayward, Helen Jervey, Nancy Kilgore, Patricia Kilgore, Pete Kilgore, Muriel McAuley, de Veax Riddick, Pat Sharp, Randy Strawderman, and Tafi Yourtee. Also arranged by size: Photographs 8 1/2" x 11" (Boxes 69-70), then 11" x 17" (Box 71).
    - Albertia, Bob (Box-folder 69:1a)
    - Ball, Helen (Box-folder 69:1)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah, and Eugenia Rowls (Box-folder 69:2)
    - Bass, Tom (Box-folder 69:3)
    - Boschen, Steve (Box-folder 69:4)
    - Brush, Charlie (Box-folder 69:5)
    - Burn, Ron (Box-folder 69:6)
    - Chadwell, Betsy (Box-folder 69:7)
    - Cherry, Jeanne (Box-folder 69:8)
    - Collins, Mary Brinklow (Box-folder 69:8a)
    - Collison, Danny (Box-folder 69:9)
    - Conklin, Bob (Box-folder 69:10)
    - Crone, Glen (Box-folder 69:11)
    - Crump, Julie (Box-folder 69:11a)
    - Dance, Bill (Box-folder 69:11b)
    - Driver, Del (Box-folder 69:12)
    - Dunaway, Kenny (Box-folder 69:13)
    - Edwards, Burt (Box-folder 69:14)
    - Evans, Madge (Box-folder 69:15)
    - Freeman, Mallory (Box-folder 69:16)
    - Fritzland, Alice (Box-folder 69:17)
    - Fulcher, Julie (Box-folder 69:18)
    - Hamblet, Bobbie and Carol (Box-folder 69:19)
    - Harris, Mary (Box-folder 69:20)
    - Haseltine, Fred (Box-folder 69:21)
    - Haylock, John (Box-folder 69:2)
    - Hayward, Don (Box-folder 69:23)
    - Hayward, Helen (Box-folder 69:24)
    - empty (Box-folder 69:25)
    - Hewitt, Thomas (Box-folder 69:26)
    - Holloway, Tom (Box-folder 69:27)
    - Huie, Michael (Box-folder 69:28)
    - Jervey, Helen (Box-folder 69:29)
    - Jeter, Allen (Box-folder 69:30)
    - Joel, Merry (Box-folder 69:30a)
    - Keys, Will (Box-folder 69:31)
    - Kilgore, Nancy and Pete, and Muriel McAuley (Box-folder 69:32)
    - Kilgore, Nancy (Box-folder 69:33)
    - Kilgore, Pete (Box-folder 69:34)
    - Kilgore, Priscilla (Box-folder 69:35)
    - Lewis, Neil (Box-folder 69:36)
    - Lindeman, Edith (Box-folder 69:37)
    - Lodge, Marion (Box-folder 69:38)
    - Lundy, Jay (Box-folder 69:39)
    - Marks, Liz (Box-folder 69:40)
    - Marvel, L. Vernon (Box-folder 69:41)
    - McAuely, Muriel (Box-folder 69:42)
    - McClary, George (Box-folder 69:43)
    - McElya, Mitchel R. (Box-folder 69:44)
    - McPhail, Ralph (Box-folder 69:45)
    - Palmore, Fritz (Box-folder 69:46)
    - Parr, James (Box-folder 69:47)
    - Pettinger, Betty (Box-folder 69:48)
    - Pick, Merry Jane (Box-folder 69:49)
    - Pollard, Suzanne Preston (Box-folder 69:50)
    - Porterfield, Bob (Box-folder 69:51)
    - Richman, Burt (Box-folder 69:52)
    - Riddick, de Veaux (Box-folder 69:53)
    - Roman, Susan (Box-folder 69:54)
    - Rothenberg, William (Box-folder 69:55)
    - Rowe, Ales (Box-folder 69:56)
    - Rowe, Hansford (Box-folder 69:57)
    - Schroll, Charlie and Mary (Box-folder 69:57a)
    - Schutte, Bernard (Box-folder 69:58)
    - Sharp, Pat (Box-folder 69:59)
    - Sharp, Pat, and Bob McElya (Box-folder 69:60)
    - Shockley, Lloyd (Box-folder 69:60a)
    - Strawderman, Randy, and Bill Black (Box-folder 69:61)
    - Sullivan, Bill (Box-folder 69:62)
    - Thomas, Buddy (Box-folder 70:1)
    - Thompson, Jeanne (Box-folder 70:2)
    - Treacy, Laura (Box-folder 70:3)
    - Vetter, Gina (Box-folder 70:4)
    - Vetter, Marty (Box-folder 70:5)
    - Wade, Tom (Box-folder 70:6)
    - Wessells, Francis (Box-folder 70:7)
    - Yourtee, Tafi (Box-folder 70:8)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 70:9)
    - Caldwell, Margaret and Mary Dowd and Jeanne Schoenes (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:1)
    - Chaldwell, Betsy (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:2)
    - Clark, Kathy (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:2a)
    - Collison, John (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:3)
    - Crone, Glen (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:4)
    - Ferrell, John and John Bowyer and Finley Greene (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:5)
    - Haseltine, Fred (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:6)
    - Hayward, Helen (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:7)
    - Joel, Alan (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:8)
    - Kilgore, Pete (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:9)
    - Lowery, Joanne (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:10)
    - Lundy, Jay (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:10a)
    - Riddick, de Veuax, and Robert Watkins (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:11)
    - Sharp, Linda (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:12)
    - Strange-Boston, Meredith (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:13)
    - Ward, Judy (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:14)
    - Unidentified (OVERSIZE) (Box-folder 71:15)
  - Subseries 2: Plays 1954-1999.
    This subseries is housed in 21 boxes and arranged by size, and within each size, chronologically by date of opening. This series includes a large and fine example of photographs of many of the Barksdale Theatre shows, 1954-1999.
    Organized chronologically by show production year. Also arranged by size: Photographs 8 1/2" x 11" (Boxes 72-81), then 11" x 17" (Boxes 82-86), then 20" x 24" (Boxes 87-92).
    - Gold in the Hills 1954 September (Box-folder 72:1)
    - High Tea 1955 May (Box-folder 72:2)
    - Hay Fever 1955 June (Box-folder 72:3)
    - Antigone 1955 June (Box-folder 72:4)
    - No Time for Comedy 1955 September (Box-folder 72:5)
    - Without love 1956 February (Box-folder 72:6)
    - Ladies in Retirement 1956 February (Box-folder 72:7)
    - Antigone 1956 March (Box-folder 72:8)
    - The Rainmaker 1956 May (Box-folder 72:9)
    - Our Town 1956 May (Box-folder 72:10)
    - Bell, Book, and Candle 1956 June (Box-folder 72:11)
    - Biography 1956 September (Box-folder 72:12)
    - Don Juan in Hell 1956 October (Box-folder 72:13)
    - Silas, the Chore Boy 1956 November (Box-folder 72:14)
    - Present Laughter 1956 November (Box-folder 72:15)
    - The Little Hut 1957 January (Box-folder 72:16)
    - Portrait in Black 1957 February (Box-folder 72:17)
    - White Sheep of the Family 1957 March (Box-folder 72:18)
    - The Lady's not for burning 1957 April (Box-folder 72:19)
    - To Rise One Day 1957 May (Box-folder 72:20)
    - Dirty work at the Crossroads 1957 September (Box-folder 72:21)
    - Dangerous Corner 1957 October (Box-folder 72:22)
    - Amphitryon 38 1957 October (Box-folder 72:23)
    - The Moon is Blue 1957 November (Box-folder 72:24)
    - The Little Hut 1958 January (Box-folder 72:25)
    - The Time of the Cuckoo 1958 February (Box-folder 72:26)
    - Bus Stop 1958 March (Box-folder 72:27)
    - The Voice of the Turtle 1958 April (Box-folder 72:28)
    - O Mistress Mine 1958 May (Box-folder 72:29)
    - The Matchmaker 1958 June (Box-folder 72:30)
    - The Fourposter 1958 September (Box-folder 72:31)
    - Laura 1958 October (Box-folder 72:32)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace 1958 November (Box-folder 72:33)
    - O Mistress Mine 1959 January (Box-folder 72:34)
    - Kind Lady 1959 February (Box-folder 72:35)
    - For Love or Money 1959 March (Box-folder 72:36)
    - The Crucible 1959 April (Box-folder 72:37)
    - Duet for Two Hands 1959 May (Box-folder 72:38)
    - Clutterbuck 1959 June (Box-folder 73:1)
    - The Little Hut 1959 July (Box-folder 73:2)
    - Where's Charley? 1959 September (Box-folder 73:3)
    - Unidentified ca. 1954-1960 (Box-folder 73:4)
    - The Crucible 1960 January (Box-folder 73:5)
    - Romanoff and Juliet 1960 February (Box-folder 73:6)
    - Venus Observed 1960 March (Box-folder 73:7)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire 1960 April (Box-folder 73:8)
    - Private Lives 1960 August (Box-folder 73:9)
    - Picnic 1960 September (Box-folder 73:10)
    - Abie's Irish Rose 1960 November (Box-folder 73:11)
    - Drink to me only 1961 January (Box-folder 73:12)
    - The Rose Tattoo 1961 March (Box-folder 12a)
    - Two for the Seesaw 1961 May (Box-folder 73:13)
    - John Brown's Body 1961 July (Box-folder 73:14)
    - Born Yesterday 1961 August (Box-folder 73:15)
    - Mister Roberts 1961 October (Box-folder 73:15a)
    - The Solid Gold Cadillac 1962 January (Box-folder 73:16)
    - Leave it to Jane 1962 March (Box-folder 73:16a)
    - J.B. 1962 May (Box-folder 73:17)
    - Fallen Angels 1962 June (Box-folder 73:18)
    - Once upon a mattress 1962 September (Box-folder 73:19)
    - Critic's Choice 1963 February (Box-folder 73:20)
    - Twelve Angry Men 1963 April (Box-folder 73:21)
    - The Curious Savage 1963 June (Box-folder 73:22)
    - The Fantasticks 1963 September (Box-folder 73:23)
    - A Shot in the Dark 1963 December (Box-folder 73:24)
    - The Moon is Blue 1964 February (Box-folder 73:25)
    - Gideon 1964 April (Box-folder 73:26)
    - The Little Hut 1964 August (Box-folder 73:27)
    - The Boyfriend 1964 October (Box-folder 73:28)
    - Sunday in New York 1965 January (Box-folder 73:29)
    - Oh Dad, Poor Dad, Mama's hung you in the closet and I'm feelin' so sad 1965 February (Box-folder 73:30)
    - Take Her, She's Mine 1965 April (Box-folder 73:31)
    - Come Back Little Sheba 1965 May (Box-folder 73:32)
    - Lullaby 1965 June (Box-folder 73:33)
    - O Mistress Mine 1965 July (Box-folder 73:34)
    - Tunnel of Love 1965 August (Box-folder 73:35)
    - Marriage-Go-Round 1965 September (Box-folder 73:36)
    - Never Too Late 1965 October (Box-folder 73:37)
    - Mary, Mary 1965 November (Box-folder 73:38)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf 1966 March (Box-folder 73:39)
    - Little Mary Sunshine 1966 April (Box-folder 73:40)
    - Boeing-Boeing 1966 June (Box-folder 73:41)
    - The Typists and The Tiger 1966 June (Box-folder 73:42)
    - Critic's Choice 1966 June (Box-folder 73:43)
    - Any Wednesday 1966 September (Box-folder 73:44)
    - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off 1966 October (Box-folder 73:45)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? 1967 February (Box-folder 74:1)